=My Rich Little Brother=
= أخي الغني الصغير =
=Episode 18=
= الحلقة 18 =
Come on.
هيا.
- Come on. - No.
- هيا.  - رقم.
What's this about?
ما هذا؟
It's a good thing.
انه شيء جيد.
You'll find out.
ستعرفون.
Come on.
هيا.
Yingying.
ينجينج.
I see how hardworking you've been.
أرى كم كنت تعمل بجد.
You are indeed qualified to be manager.
أنت مؤهل بالفعل لتكون مديرًا.
I admit it.
أنا أعترف بذلك.
Thank you all.
شكرا لكم جميعا.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
Zhengzheng, look.
Zhengzheng ، انظر.
This is our company's new project.
هذا هو مشروع شركتنا الجديد.
It's good.
إنه جيد.
Right?
حق؟
I'll make some food
سأعد بعض الطعام
to celebrate.
من اجل الاحتفال.
Wait, wait.
انتظر انتظر.
Zhengzheng, you almost burned down
Zhengzheng ، لقد احترقت تقريبًا
my kitchen last time you came to cook.
مطبخي آخر مرة أتيت فيها للطهي.
Why don't you let me do it?
لماذا لا تدعني أفعل ذلك؟
Rest assured, sister.
اطمئني يا أختي.
This time,
هذا الوقت،
I made sure to study cooking in advance.
لقد حرصت على دراسة الطبخ مقدما.
You won't be disappointed.
لن تخيب أملك.
Zhengzheng,
Zhengzheng ،
is this your
هل هذا لك
special meal for us?
وجبة خاصة لنا؟
But this is really the most beautiful
لكن هذا حقا أجمل
fried egg I've ever seen.
بيض مقلي رأيته من قبل.
Enjoy.
يتمتع.
Here.
هنا.
A candlelight dinner...
عشاء على ضوء الشموع ...
with my fiancé...
مع خطيبي ...
Wei Yingying.
وي ينجينج.
Hitting on my fiancé...
ضرب خطيبي ...
I'll beat you up whenever I see you.
سأضربك كلما أراك.
Let go of me! You are hurting me!
ترك لي!  أنت تؤذيني!
Don't you know
لا تعرف
that our families agreed for us to get married again?
ان اهلنا وافقوا علينا ان نتزوج من جديد؟
I am your fiancé.
أنا خطيبك.
Let go.
اتركه.
You'd better
من الأفضل لك
stay away from my woman.
ابق بعيدا عن امرأتي.
Otherwise,
خلاف ذلك،
there is nothing I won't do.
لا يوجد شيء لن أفعله.
Xin Zhengzheng,
شين تشنغ تشنغ ،
I'll show you
سأريكم
that you are wrong.
أنك مخطئ.
Yingying,
ينجينج ،
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I haven't been protecting you.
لم أكن أحميك.
Zhengzheng.
Zhengzheng.
You should go.
يجب أن تذهب.
Go to her.
اذهب اليها.
You two are a better match.
أنتما الاثنان أفضل مباراة.
Yingying.
ينجينج.
I'll leave now.
سأغادر الآن.
We're not a good fit.
نحن لسنا لائقين.
Our ages
عصورنا
and our families
وعائلاتنا
are in two completely different worlds.
في عالمين مختلفين تمامًا.
I've always seen you as my little brother.
لطالما رأيتك أخي الصغير.
Wei Yingying...
وي ينجينج ...
Hitting on my fiancé...
ضرب خطيبي ...
I'll beat you up whenever I see you.
سأضربك كلما أراك.
Our families agreed for us to get married again.
وافقت عائلاتنا على الزواج مرة أخرى.
I am your fiancé.
أنا خطيبك.
♪I worry if you'd get nervous♪
♪ أنا قلق إذا شعرت بالتوتر ♪
(Next episode) Stop it. Something is wrong.
(الحلقة القادمة) توقف.  هناك شئ غير صحيح.
♪When I start to lose my confidence♪
♪ عندما أبدأ في فقدان ثقتي ♪
You little brat,
أنت شقي صغير ،
are you asking for a hard time?
هل تسأل عن وقت عصيب؟
Zhengzheng.
Zhengzheng.
♪We can't let go♪
♪ لا يمكننا تركه ♪